[
    {
        "front": "Hatarakimas",
        "back": "To work",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Benkyō shimas",
        "back": "To study",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Owarimas",
        "back": "To finish",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Maiasa",
        "back": "Every morning",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Maiban",
        "back": "Every Evening",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Mainichi",
        "back": "Everyday",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Yasumi",
        "back": "Holiday, Break",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Hiruyasumi",
        "back": "Lunch break",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Yasumimas",
        "back": "To take a break",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Eki",
        "back": "Station",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Densha",
        "back": "Train",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Hikōki",
        "back": "Aeroplane",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Fune",
        "back": "Ship, boat",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Fustū",
        "back": "Local (train)",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaisoku",
        "back": "Rapid (train)",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Shinkaisoku",
        "back": "Special rapid (train)",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Shinkansen",
        "back": "Bullet Train",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Jitensha",
        "back": "Bycycle",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kare",
        "back": "He, Boyfriend",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kanojo",
        "back": "She, Girlfriend",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kazoku",
        "back": "Family",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Sengetsu",
        "back": "Last month",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kongetsu",
        "back": "This month",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Raigetsu",
        "back": "Next month",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyonen",
        "back": "Last year",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kotoshi",
        "back": "This year",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Rainen",
        "back": "Next year",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Mō",
        "back": "Already",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Nigiyaka",
        "back": "Lively",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyōshitsu",
        "back": "Classroom",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kantan",
        "back": "Simple",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Tenki",
        "back": "Weather",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Ame",
        "back": "Rain",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Ichiban",
        "back": "most-",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Hajimete",
        "back": "For the first time",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "1nen",
        "back": "1 year",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Amari",
        "back": "Not that much",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Otoko",
        "back": "Male",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Onna ",
        "back": "Female",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "IMC",
        "back": "Name of company",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kono chikaku",
        "back": "Near this area",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Niwa",
        "back": "Garden",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Yūbinkyoku",
        "back": "Post office",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Mae",
        "back": "in front of",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Zabuton",
        "back": "Sitting Cushion",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Shōmei",
        "back": "Proof",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kashikoi",
        "back": "Smart",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Uta",
        "back": "Sing",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Hako",
        "back": "Box",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Tegami",
        "back": "Letter",
        "chapter": 9
    },
    {
        "front": "Kisetsu",
        "back": "Season",
        "chapter": 9
    }
]